Email: andreea.capalnas@gmail.com

Mobile: 07525 488 997

Portfolio: andreeacapalnas.com

GitHub: /deea

LinkedIn: /andreea-capalnas

Andreea Capalnas

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Within the past three years working as Account Manager in a number of tech companies, I have developed a strong interest in being directly involved in the technical side of the product. I decided to take the next step and completed an intensive bootcamp to become a Full-Stack Developer. Having enjoyed it immensely, I am now looking to work as part of a great team to continue my journey, with a keen interest in learning new technologies, programming languages and frameworks.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Le Wagon - Part-time Teaching Assistant (OCT 2019 - Present, London)

• Teaching Assistant at London's number 1 coding Bootcamp

Le Wagon Full-stack Ruby on Rails Bootcamp (JUL 2019 - SEP 2019, London) - 9 week intensive coding bootcamp learning and coding with Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS/SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, jQuery, SQL, PostgreSQL, MVC, OOP, git, GitHub and Heroku. During the course I completed the following projects:

- Plantis A web application designed to help people look after their house plants by reminding them when each one requires watering. There is a motivational reward system in place along with a social feature where you can see and follow other people and their plants. Built with Ruby on Rails, HTML, JavaScript ES6, CSS, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap, Heroku
- Plantza In a team of four, within a week we launched an AirBnB like web app for renting/letting house plants, using Ruby on Rails, HTML, JavaScript ES6, CSS, MVC, PostgreSQL, Heroku and Figma

SKILLS

Technical | Transferable | Interpersonal - Ruby | Rails | HTML5 | CSS/SCSS |

JavaScript ES6 | PostgreSQL | Heroku | GitHub | git | DNS | Relationship Management | Project

Management | Collaboration | Teamwork | Work Ethic | Positive Attitude

PREVIOUS WORK

MarkMonitor - Domain Client Services Manager (SEP 2017 - MAY 2019, London)

- Developed and maintained strong, long-term relationships with multinational Clients and effectively managed their domain portfolios
- Project managed complex domain migration projects concurrently from start to finish, ensuring timely implementation of project deliverables

 Worked cross-functionally to resolve Customer business issues and helped achieve their stated goals

Deko - Account Manager (SEP 2015 - SEP 2017, London)

 Managed Client accounts within a fin-tech provider and worked closely with Developers regarding building new features

Atlantis Healthcare - Solutions Executive (OCT 2013 - SEP 2015, London)

• Developed my interest in Account Management along with product involvement, as I liaised with Clients and with Graphic Designers, Translators and Tech Teams alike

Serco Global Services

- Marketing Coordinator (DEC 2011 JUN 2013, London)
- HR and Employee Engagement Administrator (SEP 2010 DEC 2011, Manchester)
- Senior Service Professional and Acting Team Manager (SEP 2008 SEP 2010, London)
 - Progressed through different roles and areas of the company to learn new skills and identify what position would be best suited for me

EDUCATION

UBB, Babeș-Bolyai University, Cluj — Bachelor Degree, 2007

• Humanities: Spanish and English Philology

INTERESTS

Environmental Welfare, Volunteering, Traveling, Music Romanian (native) Festivals

LANGUAGES

Fluent in **English**, **Spanish**,

REFERENCES

Can be provided on request